Guide to the New York State Teachers Association Records 1915-1979
New York State Teachers Association Records
- Series VI: Communication and Legislation Files
  - Sub-Series B: Hopkins Subject Files, 1969-1972
    - Unsorted Information (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Education Panorama (Box 133, Folder 3)
      tape and unsorted documents
  - Sub-Series C: News Clippings, 1970-1972
    This series contains newpaper clippings related to Association and teacher activities in New York State
    - Newsclippings, 1970-1972 (Box 134, Folder 1)
- Series VII: Professional and Regional Services Files
  - Sub-Series A: Directors Files
    - Sub-Series a: Weeks Subject Files, 1958-1964
      This series contains Miss Zoraida Weeks files as director of regional field services. It includes correspondence and memos, although the bulk of the material is reports and information bulletins. The files of john degregio (field rep.) and some early files of Dean Streiff (next director) are also included. The files are arranged alphabetically by key word.
      - Council for Administrative Leadership (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Council for Administrative Leadership (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Committee on Standards for Affiliation (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Committee on Affiliates Questionnaire (Box 135, Folder 4)
        5/13/60
      - Albany Regional white House Conference (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - American Citizenship (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - American Education Week (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Committee on Association Organization and Structure (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - James M. Balassone-Memos (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Board of Directors (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Board of Directors, 1963-4 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      - Board of Directors 1963-4 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      - Board of Directors 1963-4 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Board of Directors 1963-4 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Budgets 1962-3 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Calendar 1961-2 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Calendar 1962-3 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - Certification for Teachers (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Committee on Advancement of American Citizenship (Box 136, Folder 7)
        Pilot survey
      - Citizenship Committee 1959-60 (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Citizenship Education Folder (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Classroom Teachers (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - C.T.A. of NYS (Box 136, Folder 11)
      - Classroom Teachers council 1961-62 (Box 136, Folder 12)
      - Classroom Teachers Council 1962-3 (Box 136, Folder 13)
      - Classroom Teachers Council (Box 136, Folder 14)
      - Classroom Teachers Council (Box 136, Folder 15)
      - Classroom Teachers Council (Box 136, Folder 16)
      - Classroom Teachers Council (Box 136, Folder 17)
      - Classroom Teachers Council 1963-4 (Box 136, Folder 18)
      - CTC Subcommittee on Teacher Listing Service (Box 136, Folder 19)
      - Communications (Box 136, Folder 20)
      - Conant Report (Box 136, Folder 21)
      - CDPSA (Box 136, Folder 22)
      - Cooperative Program in Educational Administration (Box 136, Folder 23)
      - Curriculum-Science (Box 136, Folder 24)
      - Division-Zones (Box 136, Folder 25)
      - Committee on Divisions (Box 136, Folder 26)
      - Committee on Dues Structure (Box 136, Folder 27)
      - Dues committee (Box 136, Folder 28)
      - Dues Increase Committee (Box 136, Folder 29)
      - Early Secondary Education Committee (Box 136, Folder 30)
      - Educational Conference Board (Box 136, Folder 31)
      - Commission on Educational Finances (Box 136, Folder 32)
      - Committee on the Education of the Gifted (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Educational Policies (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Educational TV (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Education USA (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Elementary Education Committee (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Ethics (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Code of Ethics (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Fact Sheets 1962 (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Field Services (Box 137, Folder 9)
      - Field Workers Letters 1947-52 (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Field Reports (Box 137, Folder 11)
      - Field Service Reports (cumulative) 1945-51 (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - Field Service (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - Field Workers Reports 1952-56 (Box 137, Folder 14)
      - Field Representatives Reports 1956-60 (Box 137, Folder 15)
      - Field Representatives Reports 1960-2 (Box 137, Folder 16)
      - Filing (Box 137, Folder 17)
      - Finance Committee (Box 137, Folder 18)
      - Future Teachers of America 1962-63 (Box 137, Folder 19)
      - FTA 1963-4 (Box 137, Folder 20)
      - Graves Oath for Teachers (Box 137, Folder 21)
      - Grievance Procedures (Box 137, Folder 22)
      - Group Dynamics (Box 137, Folder 23)
      - Group Insurance (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Guidance (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Handbook Revision (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Higher Education (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Higher Education Committee 1964 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Institutions of Higher Education (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Higher Education Scholarships (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - House of Delegates 1961 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - House of Delegates 1962 Syracuse NY (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - House of Delegates 1963 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      - Size of House of Delegates (Box 138, Folder 11)
      - Incorporation of Departments (Box 138, Folder 12)
      - Committee on Incorporation of Departments 1955-8 (Box 138, Folder 13)
      - Ideas on Leadership (Box 138, Folder 14)
      - In-Service Education (Box 138, Folder 15)
      - In-Service Requirements St. Ed. (Box 138, Folder 16)
      - SED Council on Instructional Improvement (Box 138, Folder 17)
      - International Education (Box 138, Folder 18)
      - International Relations (Box 138, Folder 19)
      - Installations Ceremonies (Box 138, Folder 20)
      - Conference on Juvenile Delinquency (Box 138, Folder 21)
        May 1958
      - Leaders Conferences 1952-8 (Box 138, Folder 22)
      - Leaders Conferences 1958-61 (Box 138, Folder 23)
      - Leaders conferences 1961-2 (Box 138, Folder 24)
      - Leaders Conferences on Employee Reactions in the Public Schools (Box 138, Folder 25)
      - Leaders Workshop (Box 138, Folder 26)
      - Leadership (Box 138, Folder 27)
      - Legal Decisions and Report of Counsel (Box 138, Folder 28)
      - Legal Services (Box 138, Folder 29)
      - Legislative Bulletins 1962-3 (Box 138, Folder 30)
      - Legislative Bulletins 1964 (Box 138, Folder 31)
      - Legislative Program 1960 (Box 138, Folder 32)
      - Local Associations (Box 138, Folder 33)
      - Local Associations (Box 138, Folder 34)
      - Analysis of Local Associations 1954 (Box 138, Folder 35)
      - Local Association Analysis (Box 138, Folder 36)
      - Local Association Evaluation (Box 138, Folder 37)
      - Local Association Facts Survey (Box 138, Folder 38)
        1953-4
      - Local association Facts 1958 (Box 138, Folder 39)
      - Local Association Handbook (Box 138, Folder 40)
      - Sample Local Association Handbooks (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Local Association Program Planning (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Local Association Programs and Ideas (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Local Assn. Projects (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Local Assn. Publications (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Local Assn. Scholarship and Loan Funds (surveys) (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Local Assn. Study 1958-9 (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - Letters Received From Local Education Assn. Questionnaire (Box 139, Folder 8)
      - Standards for Local Education Assn.'s 1951 (Box 139, Folder 9)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1952-7 (Box 139, Folder 10)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1957-60 (Box 139, Folder 11)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1960-2 (Box 139, Folder 12)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1960-1 (Box 139, Folder 13)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1961-2 (Box 139, Folder 14)
      - Local Leaders Letters (Box 139, Folder 15)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1962-63 (Box 139, Folder 16)
      - Local Leaders Letters 1963-64 (Box 139, Folder 17)
      - Local Taxes (Box 139, Folder 18)
      - Long Island Field Service (Box 139, Folder 19)
        Sept 1961-Aug. 1962
      - Long Island Field Service (Box 139, Folder 20)
        1962-3
      - Long Island Field Service (Box 139, Folder 21)
        1963-4
      - Long Island Leaders Workshop (Box 139, Folder 22)
        Sept. 21, 1962
      - Horace Mann (Box 139, Folder 23)
      - Membership Participation (Box 139, Folder 24)
      - Membership (Box 139, Folder 25)
      - Membership Information 1962-3 (Box 139, Folder 26)
      - Memos on Meetings at Headquarters (Box 139, Folder 27)
      - Mental Health (Box 139, Folder 28)
      - NASSTA (Box 139, Folder 29)
      - NASSTA Evaluation of NYSTA (Box 139, Folder 30)
      - National ASCD (Box 139, Folder 31)
      - National Defense Education Act 1958 (Box 139, Folder 32)
      - NEA-American Federation of Teachers (Box 139, Folder 33)
      - NEA Convention 1961 (Box 139, Folder 34)
      - NEA Convention 1962 (Box 139, Folder 35)
      - NEA Convention 1963 (Box 139, Folder 36)
      - NEA field Assignments 1962-3 (Box 139, Folder 37)
      - NEA Field Assignments 1963-4 (Box 139, Folder 38)
      - NEA Convention-Seattle (Box 139, Folder 39)
      - NEA Instructional Conference Dec. 3-6, 1961 (Box 139, Folder 40)
      - NEA Local Assn. Project 1959-60 (Box 139, Folder 41)
      - NEA Relocations (Box 139, Folder 42)
      - National Education Assn. Reports (Box 139, Folder 43)
        independent profession vs. Trade Union
      - NEFSA-Correspondence (Box 139, Folder 44)
      - National Income (Box 139, Folder 45)
      - New Rochelle Teachers Assn. (Box 139, Folder 46)
      - New York City (Box 139, Folder 47)
      - New York City Teacher Education (Box 139, Folder 48)
      - City University of New York (Box 139, Folder 49)
      - New York State Assn. For Supervision and Curriculum Development (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, Inc. (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - NYS Budget (Box 140, Folder 3)
      - NYS Education (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - NYSSED Pilot Workshop (Box 140, Folder 5)
        South Huntington 2/5-5/59
      - NYS Institution Educators Assn. Inc. (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - NYSTA Employees (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - NYSTA Leaders Workshop Day (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - NYSTA-NEA Regional Conferences Jan. 1964 (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - NYSTA News 1953-61 (Box 140, Folder 10)
      - NYSTA News and Committee (Box 140, Folder 11)
      - NYSTA Organizational Chart (Box 140, Folder 12)
      - NYSTA Policy Statement Re Teacher-School Board Relations (Box 140, Folder 13)
      - NYSTA Staff field Assignments 1960-61 Monthly (Box 140, Folder 14)
      - NYSTA Travel (Box 140, Folder 15)
      - NYSTA Travel Service 1964 (Box 140, Folder 16)
      - New York State Teachers Retirement System (Box 140, Folder 17)
      - NYS Woman's Council (Box 140, Folder 18)
        Dept. of Commerce
      - New York University (Box 140, Folder 19)
      - Old Newsletters 1953-59 (Box 140, Folder 20)
      - Newsletters 1960 (Box 140, Folder 21)
      - Newsletters, Local Associations Loan Packet (Box 140, Folder 22)
      - Sample Local Association Newsletters (Box 140, Folder 23)
      - Committee to Study Nominations Procedure May 10, 1963 (Box 140, Folder 24)
      - Committee on Nominations Procedures (Box 140, Folder 25)
      - Noon Hour Ruling (Box 140, Folder 26)
      - Committee on Association Organization and Structure (Box 140, Folder 27)
        see also: Association
      - "Organizing for Action" survey (Box 140, Folder 28)
        Oct. 18, 1957
      - Pan American Union (Box 140, Folder 29)
      - Parliamentary Procedure Tools (Box 140, Folder 30)
      - Payroll Deduction Dues (Box 140, Folder 31)
      - Personnel Practices (Box 140, Folder 32)
      - Professional Education (Box 140, Folder 33)
        (TEPS) Committee 1960-1
      - Professional Education (Box 140, Folder 34)
        (TEPS) Committee 1961-2
      - Professional Education (TEPS) (Box 140, Folder 35)
        Committee 1962-3
      - Professional Ethics (Box 140, Folder 36)
      - Professional Qualifications for Membership in NYSTA (Box 140, Folder 37)
      - Professional Practices Act Study Packet (Box 140, Folder 38)
        1960
      - PPR R (Box 140, Folder 39)
      - Qualifications for Membership in Professional Organizations 1960-61 (Box 140, Folder 40)
      - Professional Sanctions (Box 140, Folder 41)
      - Professional Services (Box 140, Folder 42)
      - Professional Standards (Box 140, Folder 43)
      - Program Associates 1962-63 (Box 140, Folder 44)
      - Program Evaluation (Box 140, Folder 45)
      - Program Planning (Box 140, Folder 46)
      - Public Relations (Box 140, Folder 47)
      - Public Relations (Box 140, Folder 48)
      - Public Relations (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Regents Proposals for the Expansion and Improvement of Education in NYS (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Regional Office (Box 141, Folder 3)
      - Committee on Regional Offices 1961-6 (Box 141, Folder 5)
      - Committee on Regional Offices 1961-6 (Box 141, Folder 6)
      - Regional Workshops (Box 141, Folder 7)
      - Request for Services 1962-3 (Box 141, Folder 8)
      - Home for Retired Teachers 1963-4 (Box 141, Folder 9)
        York State Manor
      - Retirement Committee 1960-61 (Box 141, Folder 10)
      - Retirement Committee 1961-62 (Box 141, Folder 11)
      - Retirement Committee 1962-63 (Box 141, Folder 12)
      - Retirement Committee 1963-64 (Box 141, Folder 13)
      - Retirement Variable Annuity (Box 141, Folder 14)
      - Salary Legislation (Box 141, Folder 15)
      - Staff Meetings Staff Assignments 1963 (Box 141, Folder 16)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 141, Folder 17)
      - Staff Memos (Box 141, Folder 18)
      - Staff Memos (Box 141, Folder 19)
      - Memos to Staff (Box 141, Folder 20)
      - Staff Personnel Committee (Box 141, Folder 21)
      - Council of State Affiliates 1960-69 (Box 141, Folder 22)
      - State Aid Program (Box 141, Folder 23)
      - State Aid and School Support (Box 141, Folder 24)
      - State Education Department (Box 141, Folder 25)
      - State Education Law (Box 141, Folder 26)
      - Student Division Constitution Committee (Box 141, Folder 27)
      - SEaNYS (Box 141, Folder 28)
      - SEANYS 1962-63 (Box 141, Folder 29)
      - Student Programs (Box 141, Folder 30)
        FTA, Student NEA
      - Summer School Programs (Box 141, Folder 31)
      - SEANYS 1963-64 (Box 141, Folder 32)
      - SEANYS Exec. Board and Comm. Chairmen (Box 141, Folder 33)
        Meeting Feb 17-18, 1961
      - Advisory Board on Teacher Education (Box 141, Folder 34)
        Certification and practices
      - Teacher Placement (Box 141, Folder 35)
        Preliminary Report
      - Teacher Placement (Box 141, Folder 36)
      - Teacher Recognition Day (Box 141, Folder 37)
      - Teacher-School Board Relations (Box 141, Folder 38)
        Basic Principles
      - Teaching Competence (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - Ten Payment Salary Law '55 (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - TEPS Committee 1963-64 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - TEPS (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - New York City TEPS Conference (Box 142, Folder 5)
        Dec.1, 1962
      - New York city TEPS (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - TEPS Regional Conference (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Terminal Leave With Compensation (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - New York State Manor (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - NASA Speakers 1963 Zone Conference (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Sub-Series b: Streiff Subject Files
      - Sub-Series 1: General, 1964-1972
        This series contains the files of Dean Streiff (Director of Professional and Regional Services). They contain memos, correspondence reports and information bulletins and span the period of NYSTA's two major reorganizations in 1968 and 1970. Included are the files of Marguerite Walter concerning field service, The arrangement is alphabetic. See also: Streiff Subject Files, board of directors and Local Associations.
        - Administration-General (Box 142, Folder 12)
        - Administrative and Professional Staff (Box 142, Folder 13)
        - Committee on Status of Administrators in NYSTA (Box 142, Folder 14)
        - Advisory Council (Box 142, Folder 15)
        - Advisory Comm. Ed. Meetings (Box 142, Folder 16)
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting May 20, 1968 (Box 142, Folder 17)
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 18)
          Nov. 12, 1969
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 19)
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 20)
          Nov. 11, 1970
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Minutes (Box 142, Folder 21)
          1961-64
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Minute (Box 142, Folder 22)
          1964-71
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 23)
          2/24/71
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 24)
          3/9/71
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 25)
          4/11/71
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 26)
          1971-72
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 27)
          2/1/72
        - Council of Statewide Affiliates Meeting (Box 142, Folder 28)
        - State Affiliates General Correspondence (Box 142, Folder 29)
        - Memos to State Affiliates (Box 142, Folder 30)
        - Memos to State Affiliates (Box 142, Folder 31)
        - State Affiliates Pending (Box 142, Folder 32)
        - Services to State Affiliates (Box 143, Folder 1)
        - State Affiliates Standards (Box 143, Folder 2)
        - Albany Regional Office prior to 7/1/70 (Box 143, Folder 3)
        - Alfred E. Smith Award Committee (Box 143, Folder 4)
        - American Arbitration Assn. (Box 143, Folder 5)
        - AFT (Box 143, Folder 6)
        - American Society of Association Executives (Box 143, Folder 7)
        - Annual Report 1968 (Box 143, Folder 8)
        - Annual report (Box 143, Folder 9)
        - Annual Reports to Executive Secretary (Box 143, Folder 10)
        - Annual Reports to Executive Secretary (Box 143, Folder 11)
        - Association of Assistant Principals (Box 143, Folder 12)
          11/13/71
        - Associated Community (Box 143, Folder 13)
        - Associated Community Colleges (Box 143, Folder 14)
          prior to 7/1/70
        - ACCF (Box 143, Folder 15)
        - Awards (Box 143, Folder 16)
        - Board Policies (Box 143, Folder 17)
        - BOCES (Box 143, Folder 18)
        - Budgets (Box 143, Folder 19)
        - Budgets (Box 143, Folder 20)
        - Buffalo Regional Office (Box 143, Folder 21)
        - Arvid J. Burke Fellowship (Box 143, Folder 22)
        - Business Teachers Association of New York State (Box 143, Folder 23)
        - Bylaws Committee (Box 143, Folder 24)
        - NYSTA Bylaws Committee (Box 143, Folder 25)
        - Bylaw Proposals Mailing (Box 143, Folder 26)
        - C-1 Task Force Emergency Meetings (Box 143, Folder 27)
        - Cabinet 1967-69 (Box 143, Folder 28)
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 29)
          8/3/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 30)
          9/23/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 31)
          10/12/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 32)
          11/5/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 33)
          12/22/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 34)
          12/2/70
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 35)
          1/4/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 36)
          1/18/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 37)
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 38)
          2/17/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 143, Folder 39)
          3/1/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 1)
          3/31/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 2)
          4/12/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 3)
          5/13/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 4)
          5/18/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 5)
          5/27/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 6)
          6/7/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 7)
          6/14/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 8)
          7/19/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 9)
          Legis. Program 8/10/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 10)
          8/25/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 11)
          9/8/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 12)
          9/13/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 13)
          9/21/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 14)
          9/27/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 15)
          10/4/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 16)
          10/18/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 17)
          10/27/71
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 18)
          11/22/71
        - Cabinet Retreat (Box 144, Folder 19)
          12/14/71
        - Cabinet (Box 144, Folder 20)
        - Cabinet (Box 144, Folder 21)
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 22)
          2/29/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 23)
          3/27/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 24)
          4/3/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 25)
          4/10/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 26)
          4/18/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 27)
          4/24/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 28)
          5/8/72
        - Cabinet Meeting (Box 144, Folder 29)
          5/22/72
        - Cabinet Executive Committee (Box 144, Folder 30)
          6/14/72
        - Cabinet (Box 144, Folder 31)
          7/12/72
        - DES-Canarsie Dispute (Box 144, Folder 32)
        - Certification by Performance (Box 144, Folder 33)
          Statewide Affiliate Reaction
        - Certification Task Force (Box 144, Folder 34)
          re Standard for Licensing
        - Chancellors Hall (Box 144, Folder 35)
          Nyquist 3/24/72
        - Chapters (Box 144, Folder 36)
        - Chapters (Box 144, Folder 37)
        - Chapters (Box 144, Folder 38)
          General correspondence and materials
        - Charter Affiliates (Box 144, Folder 39)
        - LC/CUNY (Box 144, Folder 40)
          General 1970
        - LC/CUNY (Box 144, Folder 41)
        - LC/CUNY (Box 144, Folder 42)
          General 1971
        - LC/CUNY-Affiliate Agreement (Box 144, Folder 43)
        - LC/CUNY-Budget (Box 144, Folder 44)
        - LC/CUNY Election (Box 144, Folder 45)
        - LC/CUNY Election Campaign (Box 144, Folder 46)
        - LC/CUNY Election Campaign (Box 144, Folder 47)
        - LC/PSC/CUNY (Box 144, Folder 48)
        - Classroom Teachers Assn. of NYS (Box 144, Folder 49)
        - Commendation Letters from Field (Box 144, Folder 50)
        - Committee Lists 1955-63 (Box 144, Folder 51)
        - Committee Lists 1964-67 (Box 144, Folder 52)
        - Committee Lists 1968-72 (Box 144, Folder 53)
        - Community College Assn. (Box 144, Folder 54)
          3/15/71
        - Community Colleges (Box 144, Folder 55)
        - Community Colleges (Box 144, Folder 56)
        - Conference of Instruction-Regional (Box 144, Folder 57)
        - Coordinators Meeting (Box 144, Folder 58)
          10/29/71
        - Correspondence (Box 145, Folder 1)
        - Cornell (Box 145, Folder 2)
          Institute of Public employment Activities
        - Driver and Safety Educators Assn. of NYS (Box 145, Folder 3)
        - Dushane Fund (Box 145, Folder 4)
        - Election Information 1970-71 (Box 145, Folder 5)
        - Elections (Box 145, Folder 6)
        - Elections 1971-72 (Box 145, Folder 7)